Nico Coenen

21 mei 1989 Bosbeekstraat 1 3511 Kuringen

2 +32(0)494 040 359

Experience

KU Leuven Lab technician at the department Chemical Engineering,

2014 - present Division Soft Matter, Rheology and Technology.

Labo Derva nv. Quality control of mainly water samples in an accredited lab for

2012 - 2014 environmental analysis.

IMEC (internship) Six months as a R&D-contributor where I worked on a project 2011 - 2012

at the research group Solar Cells. The booklet for my Bachelor I

wrote about the work was completed in English.

Education

Prof. bachelor chemistry Katholieke Hogeschool Limburg - Diepenbeek

Completed with distinction

A2 Chemistry Vrij Technisch Instituut - Hasselt

Extra courses

Yearly update course for first aid IDEWE, 2015 and 2016 Basis- en helperscourse first aid Rode Kruis, 2014

Algemene infocyclus ontwikkelingswerk Belgisch ontwikkelingsagentschap, 2013

Voetbal initiator getuigschrift C Bloso, 2012

Personal profile

I'm a driven person met as strong points communication, professional organization and correctness. I already have several years of experience with working in different labs and have worked with many devices and learned a lot of technical skills. I'm a person who always wants to keep learning as much as possible. Besides this I like responsibility's, at my current job I'm a first aid member, in the first intervention team and help in the HSE group. Currently I'm looking for a long-term job closer to home